http://www.beckettmedia.com/privacy-policy

You are here:
Privacy Policy and Statement
Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users on Beckett's network of sites, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information.
This statement discloses the privacy practices for all of Beckett Media's Web sites.
Information We Collect
Beckett collects information in several ways from our Web sites.
During online registration, Beckett asks for your name, email address, and other personal information. You are required to provide a user ID or screen name to use while accessing parts of Beckett's Web sites. The user ID or screen name identifies you to other Beckett members. During registration you have the option of supplying us with your age and gender. You also have the option of receiving email updates in the form of the Beckett Hobby News, Product Emails, Show Emails and Third Party emails. In order to receive this email you must check the "yes" box when prompted.
After you register correctly you will be emailed a password that must be used in conjunction with your chosen user ID to access certain areas of Beckett's sites.
Please note that an e-mail address is required for a Beckett Web site membership. You will not receive your password if your e-mail address is entered incorrectly.
In addition to registration we may ask you for personal information in other instances, including (but not limited to) when you enter a survey (internal research), sweepstakes, contest or promotion sponsored by Beckett and/or our partners. Wherever Beckett collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.
In the course of using our site, we automatically track certain information about you. This information includes the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. Many sites automatically collect this information.
As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, Beckett sites use "cookies" to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that tracks the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. All sites on Beckett where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies.
Advertising networks that serve ads onto any of Beckett's sites may also use their own cookies.
Beckett's sites also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers.
If you choose to establish a credit account with us, we collect some additional information, including billing address, credit card number and credit card expiration date.
If you choose to post messages in newsgroups or leave feedback for other users, we will collect such information about you as you choose to disclose.
Some of Beckett's sites offer contests and sweepstakes in which we request certain personal information. At a minimum, the required information includes name and email address; in some cases, the user must answer mandatory survey questions about a range of other personal data. The information gathered in the entry form is used to verify the entrant's identity, to send the entrant an email notification that their entry has been received, and to contact winners and/or prize recipients. There are two situations in which Beckett will divulge this information to a third party--provided the user gives express consent:
A user may expressly choose to receive additional information from the contest sponsor, in which case the user's personally identifiable information is divulged to the advertiser.
Some of the contests may be hosted on the Beckett site but administered by the sponsor; in such cases, the information a user provides is passed on to the third party as long as that user gives express consent.
Because the rules and terms of each contest can vary, all information about each contest is clearly posted during the event. All contests and sweepstakes are conducted in full accordance with United States federal and state laws.
How does Beckett use your information?
Beckett uses any information voluntarily given by you to enhance your experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of you and the rest of our users.
Beckett utilizes information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out the Beckett Hobby News to subscribers. Third Party emails are sent to users who have opted-in to this selection only.
Beckett does internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration, during a promotion, or from our server log files. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis.
Our Disclosure of Your Information
We do not share information about individual users with any third party, except in the case of some contests and sweepstakes--and then, only with a user's express consent. Beckett does not control the practices of our advertisers. If you have questions about how one of our advertisers uses information about you when you click their ad and go to their content, please contact them directly.
Throughout the site, you are identified by your User ID. Your User ID can be used to identify your activities throughout our sites.
Beckett will disclose information, at its sole discretion, to law enforcement or other government agencies as is deemed necessary and/or appropriate.
Deleting or Changing Your Registration Information
Upon request, Beckett will remove credit card number and credit card expiration date from the membership file. Requests are to be forwarded to webmaster@beckett.com.
You may review and change your email subscriptions and/or registration information, including your password, name, address, phone number, fax number, and email address, during the checkout process.
You may change your credit card number and credit card expiration date on file by accessing the Account Summary page.
Requests for removal of your registration information does not ensure that such information will be completely removed from the Beckett system. Beckett does retain registration information as a record of all activity performed on the site. Additionally, information is retained in order to enforce the Terms of Agreement, resolve disputes and problems associated with the site.
Once posted, you cannot change or remove any public postings made in newsgroups or other message areas.
Third Party Collectors of Information.
Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are bidders, buyers or sellers on beckett.com or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy customs and policies. Since Beckett does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
Beckett Collectibles, LLC.
4635 McEwen Road
Dallas, Texas 75244
webmaster@beckett.com
Feedback
close
Full Name
Your Email
Feedback
Type the characters you see in this image
We use cookies to help personalize content, tailor and measure ads, and provide a safer experience. By navigating the site, you agree to the use of cookies to collect information. Read our Cookie Policy.
Accept & Close
